McKelvey, Jean T. Papers /3001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Cases 61-107 (Box 94)
  - PRB Case 64, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 64, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 65, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 68, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 70, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 73, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 74, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 77, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - GMC vs. Local 581 UAW, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 79, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 80, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 83, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 84, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 85, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 87, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 88, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 89, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 90, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - UAW Local 971, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 91, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 92, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 93, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 95, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - McKelvey vs. Local 600, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 96, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 99, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 103, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 104, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 105, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 106 (Box 94, Folder 36)
- Cases 108-156 (Box 95)
  - PRB Case 108, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 109, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 109, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 109, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 110, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 113, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 113, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 114-116, 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 117, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Stephen Thompson vs. International Union, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 118, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Harry Becker vs. Local 600 UAW, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 119, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 121, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 122, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 122, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 124, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Henry Noble vs. Local 233 UAW, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Local 233 UAW, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 127, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 133, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 133, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 134, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 135, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 136, 1964-1965 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Saul Jackel vs. Local 1010 UAW, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 137, 1961-1965 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 140, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 141, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 142, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 149, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 154, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Proceedings 4/22/65, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 156, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 34)
- Cases 157-199 (Box 96)
  - PRB Case 157, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 158, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 164 + 162, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 163, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 163, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 165, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 167, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 169, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 170, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 172, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 173, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 174, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 176, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - UAW Local 977, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 177, 1867 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 178, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 179, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 180, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 187, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 188, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 189, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 190, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Hopkins vs. Local 730, UAW, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 191, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 191, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 192, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 193, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 194, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 195, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Charles A. Beach vs. Local 653 (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Charles A. Beach, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 196, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 197, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 197, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 197, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 198, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 36)
  - PRB Case 199, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 37)
- Cases 200-235 (Box 97)
  - PRB Case 200, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 201, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 202, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 203, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 204, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 205, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Ann B. Dunlap, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 206, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 207, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 208, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 209, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 210, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 211, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 212, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Local 553, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 213, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Local 774 UAW, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 214, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Roy Stroud, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 215, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 217, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - James T. Waldo, vs. Local 780, UAW, 1969-1970 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 218, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 219, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 220, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 221, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Brother Walter Reuther, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 222, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 223, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 224, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 225, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 226, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 227, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 33)
  - Leonard T. Poynter vs. Local 408, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 228, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 229, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - PRB Case 230, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 37)
  - PRB Local 232, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 38)
  - PRB Case 233, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 39)
  - PRB Case 234, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 40)
  - PRB Case 235, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 41)
- Cases 236-261 (Box 98)
  - PRB Case 236, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 237, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 237, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 238, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 239, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 240, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 241, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 242, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 243, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Gilbert Grijalva, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Appeal Case M-35, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 244, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 245, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 245, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 246, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 247, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 248, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - UAW Local 163, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - UAW Local 163, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - UAW Local 163, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - UAW Local 163, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - UAW Local 163, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - William A. Kiel, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - UAW Local 163, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 251, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Al Piluso Local 738, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Walter P. Reuthner, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 254, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 255, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 256, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 257, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - Local 887, UAW, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 257, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 259, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 260, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 261, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 36)
- Cases 262-292 (Box 99)
  - PRB Case 262, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 262, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 263, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - PRB - UAW, 1970-1972 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 264, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 265, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 266, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 267, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 268, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 269, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 270, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 271, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 272, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 273, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 274, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 275, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Ralph Nader, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Jim Townsend, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 276, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 277, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 278, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 279, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 280, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 281, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 282, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - Local 235, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 283, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 284, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 28)
  - UAW Local 3, 1966-1969 (Box 99, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 285, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 286, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 287, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 288, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 289, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 290, 1972-1974 (Box 99, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 291, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 36)
  - PRB Case 292, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 37)
  - PRB Case 293, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 38)
  - PRB Case 294, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 39)
  - UAW General Election Results '71, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 40)
- Cases 293-321 (Box 100)
  - PRB Case 295, 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 296, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 297, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 297, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 298, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 299, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 299, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 300, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 301, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 302, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 303, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 304, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Alfonso Badalemento, 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 305, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 306, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Local 488, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 307, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 308, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 309, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Dominic Swaldi Jr., 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 310, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 310, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 311, 1973-1974 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 312, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - PRB Cases 313 + 316, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 314, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 315, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 315, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 316, 1973-1974 (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 316, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 30)
  - PERB Case 313, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 318, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 32)
  - Donald Bishop, Local 997, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 319, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 320, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 321, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 36)
  - PRB Case 322, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 37)
- Cases 322-339 (Box 101)
  - PRB Case 322, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 323 + 324, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 325, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 326, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Local 117, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 327, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Ethical Practices Complaint, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 327, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 328, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 329, 1971-1975 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Local 160, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 330, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 331, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 332, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 332, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 333, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 334, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 334, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 335, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 336, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - Local 171 UAW, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 337, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 338, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 339, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 339, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - Local 412, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 26)
- Cases 340-374 (Box 102)
  - PRB Case 340, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 341, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 342, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Local 14 U.A.W., 1974 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 343, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 344, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 345-348, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Local Union 738, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 346, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 347, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 349, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 349, 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 350, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 351, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 352+353, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 354, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 355, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 356, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 357, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 358, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 359, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 360, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 361, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 362, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 363, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 364, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 365, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 366, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 367, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 368, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 369, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 370, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 370, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 371, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 372, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 373, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 36)
  - PRB Case 374, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 37)
  - PRB Case 374, 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 38)
- Cases 375-399 (Box 103)
  - PRB Case 375, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Local Union 974, U.A.W., 1978 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Local Union 974, UAW, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 377+378, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 379, 1976-1977 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 380, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 381, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Notes, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 382, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 383, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 383, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 383, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 384, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 385, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Local 157, UAW, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 386, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 387, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 388, 1976-1977 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Local 222 U.A.W., 1972 (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 389, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 390, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 391, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 392, 1976-1977 (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 393, 1976-1977 (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 394, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 395, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 396, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 397, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 398, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 399, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 30)
- Cases 400-422 (Box 104)
  - PRB Case 400, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 401, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Public Review Board, 1972-1976 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 402, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Local 283, 1975-1976 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 404, 1976-1977 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Rudolph Coleman, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 403 + 405, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 406, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 407, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - U.A.W. Local 153, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 408, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 408, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 409, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 410, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 411, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 412, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 412, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Lynn Pullinam vs. Local 933, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Local Union 699, UAW, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - Local Union 326, U.A.W. Case 415, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 416, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 416, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 417, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 418, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 419, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 420, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 27)
  - Local 296, U.A.W., 1976 (Box 104, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 421, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 422, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 30)
- Cases 423-448 (Box 105)
  - PRB Case 423, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Local Union 422, U.A.W., 1976 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 424, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 425, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 426, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 427, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 428, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 429, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 430, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 430, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 431, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 432, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Memorandum of Understanding, 1975-1978 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 433, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 434, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 434, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - U.A.W. Local 1112, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Local 1112, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 435, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 436, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 437, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 438, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 439, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 439, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 440, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 441, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 441, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 441, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 442, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 443, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 444, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 445, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 446, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 447, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 448, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 35)
- Cases 449-471 (Box 106)
  - PRB Case 449, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 449, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 450, 1976-1977 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 451, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 452, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 453, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 454, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Misc., 1971-1977 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 454, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 455, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 456, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Local 622 U.A.W., 1977 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 457, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - U.A.W., 1978 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 458, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Livonia Plant, 1970-1976 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 459, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 460, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Local 723, U.A.W., 1978 (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 461, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Misc. 461, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - J.L. Mingo, 1977-1978 (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 462, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - U.A.W. Local 387, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 463, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 464, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 465, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 28)
  - Local Union 1459, U.A.W. 466, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 467, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 468, 1980 (Box 106, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 469, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 32)
  - U.A.W. Local 1069 - election, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 470, 1980 (Box 106, Folder 34)
  - U.A.W. Local 248, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 471, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 36)
- Cases 472-500 (Box 107)
  - PRB Case 472, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Local 2000 U.A.W., 1978 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 473, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 474, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Local Union 1364, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 475, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 475, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 476, 1978-1979 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Local Union 148, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 477, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 478, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 479, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Local 952, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Local Union 72, U.A.W. Case 481, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Local 72, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 482, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 483, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 484, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Local 245 U.A.W., 1977 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 485 + 501, 1978-1980 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 487, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Local 699, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - Local 699, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 488, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 489, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 490, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 491, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 492, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 493, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 494, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 495, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 496, 1979-1980 (Box 107, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 497, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 498, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 499, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 500, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 36)
  - PRB Case 541, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 37)
- Cases 501-516 (Box 108)
  - PRB Case 501, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 501, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 502, 1977-1978 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 503, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 503, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Local 644 U.A.W., 1981 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 504, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - President's Chrysler Local Unions, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 505, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 506, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 506, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 507, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Local 81, 1977 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 508, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 509, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 509, 1976 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Local 412, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Chrysler Corp., 1976 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 510, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 511, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 512, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 512, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 513, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 513, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 514, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 515, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 516, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 27)
- Cases 517-546 (Box 109)
  - PRB Case 517, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 518, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 519, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 520, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 521, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 522, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 523, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Local 1364, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 524, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 525, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 526, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 527, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Local 1152, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 528, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 14)